Fausold, Martin; Papers ua902.078
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- FASUNY, 1948-1969; Undated; 3; 2 cubic ft.
  - Correspondence, Bronston-Cahill, 1964-1969 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Campbell-Cherkauer, 1964-1967 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Clinton-Curtis, 1964-1967 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Daiger-Fried, 1964-1967 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Frost-Gorman, 1964-1968 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Gould-Hauser, 1964-1967 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Hawkin-Hirsch, 1965-1968 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Hoagland-Klein, 1964-1967 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Kolby-Loubere, 1963-1967 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Mackenzie-Martens, 1964-1967 (Box 1 (3-FASUNY), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Martin-Orwen, 1964-1967 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Palmer-Pitaro, 1964-1967 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Price-Sanders, 1963-1967 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Satre-Sherwig, 1963-1969 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Sherwin-Vukasin, 1964-1968 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Wachman-Zeller, 1965-1967 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 6)
  - FASUNY Elections, 1965-1967 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 7)
  - FASUNY Government, 1966 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 8)
  - FASUNY Legal Hearings, 1968 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 9)
  - FASUNY Meeting Minutes, 1964-1966 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 10)
  - FASUNY Meeting Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 11)
  - FASUNY Membership, 1960-1968 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 12)
  - FASUNY Membership Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 13)
  - FASUNY News, 1965-1966 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 14)
  - FASUNY Newsletters, 1957-1968 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 15)
  - FASUNY Pamphlets, 1962-1963; 1967-1968; Undated (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 16)
  - Freda Martens, 1963-1965 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 17)
  - Newsletter Mailing Lists, 1965-1967 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 18)
  - New York Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 19)
  - Payroll Deduction, 1965 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 20)
  - Personnel Policy, 1964-1966 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 21)
  - Professional Education, 1965; 1995 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 22)
  - Purchasing, 1966 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 23)
  - Regents Plan, 1964-1965 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 24)
  - Salary Reports, 1959 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 25)
  - Salary Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 26-27)
  - Summer Sessions Policy Committee, 1955; 1959 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 28)
  - SUNY, 1964-1966 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 29)
  - Wells Committee Report, 1964 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 30)
  - 1966-1967 SUNY Budget Request, 1965 (Box 2 (3-FASUNY), Folder 31)
- 1991 Brockport Conference, 1982; 1989-1991; Undated; 4; 0.33 cubic ft.
  The fourth series of the collection contains papers from The Coming of SUNY Conference hosted at SUNY Brockport in 1991. This conference is particularly important as it was one of the first efforts to gather historians and archivists to discuss the founding and history of the SUNY System. The conference program as well as a list of participants is included in this series. Papers and abstracts listed in the program are also included in this series as well as some of Fausold's personal notes on each.
  - Brockport Conference Program, 1991 (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 1)
  - Concepts of State University of New York at Its Beginning by Freda Martens, 1989 (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 2)
  - Conference Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 3)
  - Conference Participants, 1991 (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 4)
  - Conference Planning Outlines, Undated (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 5)
  - Cornell University: SUNY Foregone, Undated (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 6)
  - Discussion-The Coming of SUNY Twentieth Century Precursors and the Founding of SUNY, 1991 (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 7)
  - The Morrill Act and its Impact on New York's Public Higher Education by G. Colman, Undated (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 8)
  - The New York State Normal Schools and the Development of Higher Education by Mitchell Robinson, 1990 (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 9)
  - Oral History Revelations of Early SUNY by Martin Fausold, 1991 (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 10)
  - Politics and the Development of the SUNY System by Jeffrey Stonecash, 1991 (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 11)
  - Prologue to American Higher Education and its Implication for Higher Education by Edwin Duryea, 1982 (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 12)
  - The Regent and the French (and other) Connections by Charles Bailey, Undated (Box 1 (4-1991 Brockport Conference), Folder 13)